("Mr. Brightside" by The Killers)
♪ Coming out of my cage ♪
♪ And I've been doing just fine ♪
♪ Gotta gotta be down ♪
♪ Because I want it all ♪
♪ It started out with a kiss ♪
♪ How did it end up like this ♪
♪ It was only a kiss, it was only a kiss ♪
♪ Now I'm falling asleep ♪
♪ And she's calling a cab ♪
♪ While he's having a smoke ♪
♪ And she's taking a drag ♪
♪ Now they're going to bed ♪
♪ And my stomach is sick ♪
♪ And it's all in my head ♪
♪ But she's touching his chest now ♪
♪ He takes off her dress now ♪
♪ Let me go ♪
♪ And I just can't look, it's killing me ♪
♪ And taking control ♪
♪ Jealousy, turning saints into the sea ♪
♪ Swimming through sick lullabies ♪
♪ Choking on your alibis ♪
♪ But it's just the price I pay ♪
♪ Destiny is calling me ♪
♪ Open up my eager eyes ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm Mr. Brightside ♪
♪ I'm coming out of my cage ♪
♪ And I've been doing just fine ♪
♪ Gotta gotta be down ♪
♪ Because I want it all ♪
♪ It started out with a kiss ♪
♪ How did it end up like this ♪
♪ It was only a kiss, it was only a kiss ♪
♪ Now I'm falling asleep ♪
♪ And she's calling a cab ♪
♪ While he's having a smoke ♪
♪ And she's taking a drag ♪
♪ Now they're going to bed ♪
♪ And my stomach is sick ♪
♪ And it's all in my head ♪
♪ But she's touching his chest now ♪
♪ He takes off her dress now ♪
♪ Let me go ♪
♪ 'Cause I just can't
look, it's killing me ♪
♪ And taking control ♪
♪ Jealousy, turning saints into the sea ♪
♪ Swimming through sick lullabies ♪
♪ Choking on your alibis ♪
♪ But it's just the price I pay ♪
♪ Destiny is calling me ♪
♪ Open up my eager eyes ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm Mr. Brightside ♪
♪ I never ♪